SM TURAG

FULL STACK WEB & ANDROID APPS DEVELOPER

CONTACT

01605042408

 \bowtie

smturag0@gmail.com



https://smturag-cpreeu3afsmturag.vercel.app/



https://github.com/smturag



Rangpur

SKILLS

- Language: C, JavaScript, PHP,
- Frameworks: React, React Native, Laravel, Express JS with Prisma, Next is
- Database: SQL, NoSQL
- Version Control: Git & Github, BitBucket
- Having basic of JAVA, Android.

EDUCATION

BSC In CSE

Daffodil international University

2016-2020

Dhanmondi, Dhaka

HSC in Science

Rangpur Govt College

2012-2014

Rangpur

LANGUAGES

Bangla

English





PROFILE

Full Stack Web Developer specializing in front end & backend development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP OOP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL. Strongbackground in project management and customer relations.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software developer

IT Deal LTD

Rangpur

- ECommerce project development
 - React, Redux
- · Working on SASS based project
 - Laravel
- Working On loan collection apps
 - React-Native, Redux
- · Working on existing project
- Database collaboration

Software developer (intern)

Bitbytesoft Company LTD

Germany

- Laravel Development
- Web Scrapping
- Sximo service

1/4/2022-1/8/2022

1/8/2022-- Current